QUARK: On the orders of Dominator Toba,
按统领者 Toba 的命令
the building was destroyed,
该建筑已被摧毁
also the man Cully.
以及人类 Cully
- But Jamie was in that building!
- Silence!
- 但 Jamie 在那个建筑里！ - 安静！
You deliberately disobeyed my order?
你故意不遵守我的命令？
My life was threatened
and the Quark destroyed.
我的性命受到了威胁，夸克摧毁了它
Yes, because of your own actions.
是的，因为你擅自行动
Are you suggesting
I should have let him escape?
你是在暗示我应该放任他逃走？
And where would he have gone?
We are on an island, Toba.
他又能跑哪儿去？我们在一个岛上，Toba
These creatures cannot escape.
这些生物逃不了
Now listen to me carefully,
现在仔细听我说
and this time you will obey my instructions.
这一次你要服从我的指示
Send these creatures back
to the central bore position.
把这些家伙送回中央矿洞位置
I want it cleared, ready for drilling.
我期望那里清理处理，为钻孔做好准备
But the Quarks will do it more quickly.
但夸克可以做得更快
We must conserve their energy
for drilling purposes.
我们必须保留他们的能量，留给钻孔用
You know the power levels are low.
你知道它们的能量值很低
Command accepted.
命令已接受